Guide to the African Collection, Yale University Library, Records of the Curator
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1965-1990; Accession 1998-A-127
  - Miami University, Oxford, Ohio (M. William Swanson), 1970–1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Michigan State University, 1995–1997 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Michigan University (Ann Arbor), 1967–1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Michigan State University African Studies Center, 1979–1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Micro Africa, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Microform Academic Publishers, 1990–1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regional Africanist Association, 1982 May 18 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Middle East Librarians Association, 1981–1985 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Middlebury College, Vermont, 1975–1995 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Mid-West University, Benin City, 1970 November 5 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Miller, Dr. A. Robert, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Ministry of Environment and Tourism, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1979–1990 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991–1998 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Missouri University, 1980–1991 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Mohammed V. Universite, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Mohlamme, Jacob S., 1986 September 2 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Montreal Universite, 1981 August 27 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Morgan State University, 1985 March 8 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Morocco Bibliotheque Generale et Archives, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Mossolow, N., 1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1980–1987 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Mouvement Anti-Apartheid de Suisse, 1979–1985 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Murray, Joseph N., 1994 September 30 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Musee Barbier-Mueller, 1993–1997 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Museum for African Art, Undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Musée royal de l'Afrique centrale, 1985–1997 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Nedeco (Netherlands Engineering Consultants), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Nairobi, University of, 1967–1990 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Nairobi University Press, Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Namibia Christian Exchange, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Namibia Communications Centre, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Namibia Information Service, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Namibian National Students Organization, 1992 September 17 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Namibia News Bureau, 1987 February 24 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Naples University, 1986–1996 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - The Natal Witness Printing & Publishing Company, 1992 December 14 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - University of Natal, 1991 January–1993 December (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - University of Natal, 1976–1989 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Natal University Institute for Social Research, 1965–1977 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - University of Natal Press, 1994 May 26 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Natal Museum, Pietermaritzburg, 1968–1977 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - The Natal Society, 1970–1997 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - National Archives of Namibia, 1990–2002 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - National Bureau Education & Social Research (South Africa), 1966–1968 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - National Chengchi University, 1972–1975 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - National Committee Against Removals, 1986 January 28 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1980–1990 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - The National English Literary Museum, 1990–1993 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - National Film & Television School, 1984 May 11 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - The National Library, 1994 September 20 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - National Council for Scientific Research, Lusaka, 1977 May 30 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - National Development and Management Foundation of South Africa, 1972–1977 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - National Endowment for Democracy, 1987 February 23 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1987 May 4 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - National Endowment for the Arts - Thurston, 1987–1990 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - National Film Board, Pretoria, 1974–1998 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - National Forum Foundation, 1986 February 25 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - National Geographic, 1979 April 4 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - National Institute for Personnel Research, 1977–1985 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - National Land Committee, 1990 June 26 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - National Library of Canada, 1976–1989 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - National Library of Nigeria - Lagos, 1968–1985 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - National Library of Scotland, 1981 April 23 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - National Microfilm Library, 1975 May 27 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - National Museum of African Art and Library - Smithsonian Institution, 1990–1997 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - National Productivity Institute, Pretoria, 1974–1977 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - National Resource Center in African Studies, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Nebraska-Lincoln University, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Nehru Memorial Museum and Library - Sharma, Mrs. Aruna, 1997 September (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Neue Zeitschrift fur Missionswissenschaft, 1981 April 12 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - University of New England - Armidale, Australia, 1980–1981 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - New Hampshire University, 1984–1990 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - University of New Haven, 1988 November 12 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - New Haven Colony Historical Society, Undated (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Newick Park initiative, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - New World Resource Center - Chicago, 1972–1987 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - New Writers' Group, 1971–1972 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - New York African Studies Association, 1988 February 12 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - "Newspapers" articles, 1993–1994 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Dauphin, Joanne, 1990–1994 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990–1991 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Nedbook International, 1996 December (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Newark Public Library, New Jersey, 1969 January 10 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Newspapers, 1993–1995 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - New York University, 1975–1996 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - New York Public Library, 1966–1987 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Newfoundland, Memorial University of, 1989 June (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Ngambe Group, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Niagara University, 1983–1984 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Nigerian Book Foundation Ike, Professor Chukwuemeka, President, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - University of Nigeria, 1964–1996 (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Nordiska Afrikainstitutet (The Scandanavian Institute of African Studies), 1963–1994 (Box 17, Folder 100)
  - Northern Arizona University, 1970–1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Olden, Anthony, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - O'Neil, Fr. Robert, 1988–1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Draft Recommendations from Orbis Review Group, 1990 December 12 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Organization of African Unity, 1965–1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Service Pensioners Benevolent Society, 1976 March 9 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Peeters, Father H., 1988–1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania University Library, Philadelphia, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Phuthadikobo Museum, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Princeton University Library, 1979–1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Public Record Office II, London, 1977–1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Dr. T.G. Ramamurthi, 1991 May 9 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Research Libraries Group Africa Interest Group, 1980–1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Research Libraries Group Collection Development, 1975–1985 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Research Libraries Group Consepctus, 1983–1985 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Research Libraries Group Serials Task Force, 1975–1988 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Robson, John F. United Nations, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller University, 1991–1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Rodwell, Edward, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Rosenthal Eric Africana Collection, 1985 February 20 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - South Africa Liberation Information Group (SALIG), circa 1970s (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Schomburg Center, New York Public Library, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Mr. A.H.M. Kirk-Greene, St. Antony's College, 1990–1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Salamon, Larry Mr., 1990–1998 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Mr. John S. Saul, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Shaw University, 1997 June 18 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Sheffield University, 1982–1984 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Sketch-Map Publishing Enterprises, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Society for Libyan Studies, 1975–1982 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Somalia, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Southern Connecticut State College, 1969–1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Stanford University, California, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - State University of New York-Buffalo, 1980–1988 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Stellenbosch University Library, 1988–1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Strathmore College, Nairobi, 1977–1982 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Mr. Qasim Osman Nur Sudan Publications, 1989–1998 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Sugar Industry Research Institute, 1980–1981 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Surplus People Project, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Sussex University Institute of Development Studies Library, 1975–1979 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - University of Sydney, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Tanzania Library Service, 1975–1981 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Taylor, Catherine Correspondence, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Catalogue des Publications du Musée royal de l'Afrique centrale, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Terrorism Research Centre/Associates, 1983–1988 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Texas, University at Austin, 1970–1971 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Third World Reports, 1994–1996 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Dennis Duerden-Transcription Centre, 1969–1972 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - United Nations-Section for African Questions & Unit on Apartheid, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Yale-Libraries Accessions Lists, 1965–1975 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Yale University Library Administration, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Yale Library Research Colloquia, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Student Employment Procedures 1991/92 Academic Year, 1990–1991 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Yale University Library Personnel, 1986–1996 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Yale University Library Medical Library, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Yale University Library Music Library, 1971–1992 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Yale University Library Divinity (SDQ), 1977–1997 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Yale: Afro-American Studies Department, 1980–1989 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Yale University Library Art Library, 1994–1996 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Yale University Art, Art Department, Art Gallery, Art History, 1978–1988 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Yale History Department, Political Science Department, Social Sciences, 1979–1980 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Yale University Language Lab, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - A.C.R.P.P., 1973–1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - A La Decouverte, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Abbas, A.S., 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Richard Abed & Co. Inc., 1970–1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Africa Agency, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Africa Bureau, London, 1966–1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Africa Publications Trust, 1982–1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Africa South Books, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - African Books in Print, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - AILS Nigeria Project, 1980–1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Kansas University Library Lawrence, Kansas, 1966–1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Cindy Kaplan, Producer Haworth Shakespeare Festival, 1990–1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Kenneth Karmiole, Bookseller, Inc., 1990 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Kenya Institute of Administration, 1971–1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Kenya Methodist University, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Kenya National Academy for Advancement of Arts & Sciences, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Kenya National Academy of Sciences, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Kenya National Archives, 1980–1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Kenya National Museum, 1975–1987 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Kenya National Library Services, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Kenyatta University, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Mr. Qasim Osman Nur, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Kenyatta University College Library, Nairobi, 1977–1985 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Khartoum University Library, 1964–1986 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - King's College Library, London, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Universite de Kisangani, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Kivu Koni College, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Klein, Carole, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Koel Report Folder, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - KOERS Bulletin for Christian Scholarship, circa 1991 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Koenig, Christian Mr., 1994–1998 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Mr. Peter Kohler, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Koninklijk Instituut Voor De Tropen-Amterdam, 1971–1976 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Knowledge Resources, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Kreike, Emmanuel, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Mr. Darrell Kruger, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - KTM Incorporated, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Kudirka, Nijole, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Kultura, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Kumasi, Ghana University of Science and Technology, 1964–1973 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Kyoto University, Japan, 1970–1983 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - United States Committee for Refugees, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - United States Department of Education, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - United States Department of Educational and Cultural Foundation in Liberia, 1985–1986 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - United States Information Agency, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - United States/Namibia (South West Africa) Trade & Cultural Council, Inc., 1982 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - United Nations Centre for Human Settlements (Habitat), 1994 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - United Nations Environment Programme, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - UNOSOM United Nations Operation in Somalia, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - United States Department of Education, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - United States-South Africa Leader Exchange Program (USSALEP), 1980–1986 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Universidade Tecnica de Lisboa, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Universite Officielle de Bujumbura-Burundi, 1974–1980 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Universita Degli Studi Di Narobi, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - University of Durban-Westvile (Documentation Centre, Library), 1994 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - University College, London, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - University Microfilms International, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - University of Namibia, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - University of the North (Turfloop, South Africa), 1976–1981 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - University Publications of America, 1992–1997 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Unterhalter, Jack, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Universidade Tecnica de Lisboa, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Uppsala University, Sweden, 1970–1986 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1969–1994 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Venmyn Rant (Pty) Ltd., 1992 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Vendor Memo Codes & Texts, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Vendor Record Update File, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Vermond, University of, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Vienna Institute for Development, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - University of Virginia, 1991–1995 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Utah State University, Logan, 1977–1990 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Virgo Limited, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Visitor Program Service of Meridian House International, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - T. Philemon Wakashe, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Walker Center for Ecumenical Affairs, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Walker, Matthew, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Wagner, Ralph D. Mr., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Warsaw University II, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Wartburg College, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 81)
  - Warwick University, 1984 August 27 (Box 19, Folder 82)
  - Dr. Ilah J. Weiblen, Coordinator Namibia Files, Wartburg Theological Seminary, 1992–1998 (Box 19, Folder 83)
  - Washington University, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Washington University in St. Louis, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - University of Waterloo, 1981–1988 (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Wayne State University, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Webster's (Pty.) Ltd., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Weisfelder, Prof. Richard F. U of Toledo, Ohio, 1976–1981 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Weiskel, Timothy C., 1966–1987 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Wesleyan University, Middletown, CT, 1990–1996 (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - West, Eugenia Mr., 1993–1994 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - West, Tina, 1987–1992 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - University of the West Indies, Trinidad, 1972–1985 (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - West Virginia University Library, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - University of Western Australia, 1988–1993 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - University of the Western Cape, 1987–1997 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Western Illinois University, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Western Michigan University Kalamazoo, Mich., 1969–1975 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Wheldon & Wesley, Limited, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - White House Library, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Mr. Timothy White, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Wingate Trust, 1995 September 11 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Williams, Mr. E.M., 1998 March 31 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Williams, Lee H., Jr., 1986–1991 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Professor Robin Winks, History Department, 1991 December 9 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Winthrop College, 1991–1993 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Wisconsin University Library, 1991–1992 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - University of the Witwaterstrand, Johannesburg, 1987–1997 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - University of the Witwaterstrand, 1993 January–1995 December (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Women Make Movies, Inc., 1997 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Work in Progress, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Women's Legal Status Committee, 1988–1990 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Worcester Art Museum, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Working Life Distributors, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - World Bank, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - World Council of Churches, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - World Health Organization, 1985–1993 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - World Peace Council, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Worldwide Documentaries, Inc., 1986 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Wright State University, Ohio, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Wylie, Diana, 1980–1988 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Zell, Hans Publishing Consultants, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Morton-Young, Tommie, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - University of Zimbabwe, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Zimbabwe International Book Fair Limited, 1993–1996 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Zimbabwe Science News, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - African Studies Association, United States IV, 1976–1992 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Book Sales-Paid, 1978–1985 (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Publishing in Africa, 1968–1973 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Students, 1977–1988 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Health Service/Workmen's Compensation Form, undated (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Forms for applications etc., 1989 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Equipment Status Forms, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Personnel-samples file, 1979–1988 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Yale Memoranda from Personnel or Administration, 1984–1988 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Time sheet samples, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Library Manual Deletions, 1979–1985 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - Library Policy Manual Deletions, 1981–1983 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - Accounting Transfers & others involving other Yale University Library, 1975–1989 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  - Yale University Law School, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Yale University Linguistics, 1982–1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Yale University Medical School, 1983–1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Yale University Music School & Dept., 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Yale University Office of Public Information, 1984–1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Yale University Philosophy Department, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Yale Psychology Department, 1983–1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Yale University Secretary, 1980–1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Yale-Timothy Dwight College, 1979–1988 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Yale University Traffic, Receiving & Stores, 1986–1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Yale University-Other Departments (English, Languages, etc.), 1978–1979 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Yale University Press, 1983–1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Yaoundé, Université de (formerly Université Federale de Cameroun), 1972–1980 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - York University, England, 1980–1988 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - York University, Ontario, 1973–1978 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Yudelman, David, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Zal Holdings Ltd., 1986–1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Zaire Universite Nationale, 1972–1980 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Universite Nationale de Zaire, 1963–1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Zambia University, 1969–1984 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Zambia Appointments Ltd., 1981–1987 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Zambia Geographical Association, 1974–1983 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - The Zambia Society, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Zell, Hans, 1990–1991 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Zimbabwe University (Salisbury), 1968–1991 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Zimbabwe National Archives, 1981–1987 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Zimbabwe National Archives, 1970–1980 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Zimbabwe Parliament Library (Salisbury), 1967–1980 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Zimbabwe-Mozambique Friendship Association, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Zimbabwe Project, 1981–1984 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Zimbabwe Scientific Association, 1981–1985 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Zululand, University of, 1969–1992 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Dealers List/Form Letter, 1972–1990 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Dealers A-M, 1973–1988 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Dealers N-Z, 1973–1989 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Publishers Correspondence A-M, 1967–1989 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous Publishers Correspondence N-Z, 1977–1987 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Periodicals & Serials III, 1976–1988 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Periodicals & Serials II, 1970–1975 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Periodicals & Serials I, 1964–1969 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Periodicals Regularly Containing Material on Africa, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Political Parties II, 1970–1975 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Political Parties I, 1964–1969 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Pressure Groups, Study Groups etc. based in U.S. or Europe, 1964–1987 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Research Organizations-Misc., 1982 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Researcher-Misc., 1981 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Right-Wing Organizations, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - South African Lists, etc., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Student Organizations, 1970–1986 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - National Union of South African Students, 1971–1978 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Television (Miscellaneous), 1983–1988 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Trade Unions, 1968–1989 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Women's Organizations, 1986–1988 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Photographic Orders Outstanding, 1982–1984 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Photographic Order-Completed, 1985–1988 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Photographic Orders Xeroxes of Bills for Checking Statements, 1983–1986 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Book Sales-Unpaid, 1979–1986 (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Administrative records of the curator of the African Collection, circa 1963-1974; Accession 2005-A-075
  The materials are open for research.
  - Acquisitions, policy, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - African collections report, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Administrative records of the curator of the African Collection, 1979-2013; Accession 2015-A-011
  Restricted until January 1, 2048
  - Aluka, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual reports
    - 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - African collection exhibits, 2001-2013 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Archibishop Desmond Tutu archive project/Yale, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)